Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 88, Folder: 8 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Contributory Annuity Plan For Sales And Service Field Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). November 1, 1942: April 1, 1945 Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: a Plan Of Group Insurance For Our Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). c.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: A Plan Of Group Insurance For Our Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: A Plan Of Group Insurance For Our Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). c.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Guide To Current NCR Books: Library, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: 75, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). November 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). As Amended October 1, 1954 and with Proposed Amendments As Of July 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). As Amended And In Effect January 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Highlights of the Revised NCR Employee Benefit Program: For "Class A, B, and C" employees of National Cash Register Co., Dayton, OH, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Effective January 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Old River, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Guide To Current NCR Books: Library, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). c.2; October 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: A Guide To New NCR Books Library, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). October 1939`. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: A Guide To New NCR Books Library, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). April 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Evening Classes: Thirty-Seventh Year Announcement of Courses 1939-1940, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Prize Catalog For The New NCR Suggestion Contest, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). April 1, 1949 To March 31, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The Founding and Building of The National Cash Register Co., Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: 1948 Personal Record of Earnings, Deductions and Expenses, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: Contributory Group Life and Accident-Sickness Insurance, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: Visiting Nurses Report, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: Group Insurance For Employees And Their Dependents, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Contributory Group Life and Accident-Sickness Insurance, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: Agreement Between The National Cash Register Co. And N.C.R. Employees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: The NCR Relief Association Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: The NCR Relief Association Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Christmas: Your Best Christmas Gift to Your Family, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: 25 Year Club: Members of the 25 Year Club Directory as of April 1, 1955, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). April 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Health and Safety: There's neither Good Health nor Bad Health- simply Health, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: Health and Safety- Care of the Eyes, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Health: Colds, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: Health: Health hints on eating, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: It's Up To You, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: Let's Pledge Ourselves in 1922, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: Health: Tuberculosis, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: 25 Year Club: Members of the 25 Year Club 1957 Directory, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Box: 88, Folder: 9 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Information and Rules for our Factory and Office Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; March 27 1923, Superseded. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rules for Success, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; March 27 1923;. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: N.C.R. Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; Feb 26 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 50-50 Profit-Sharing Plan 1924, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Owners' Profits; Employees' Profits; Industrial Relations Section; May 3rd 1924. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 50-50 Profit-Sharing Plan 1921, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Owners Profits, Employees' Profits; H.B. Bergen Collection. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: For Your Enjoyment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR Employees Benefit Association. Industrial Relations Section; Jan 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Guide for Departmental Safety Representatives, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By The NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; Jan 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Old River, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; Jan 20 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: 12th Annual Report, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; APR 20 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Your Guide to the Employee and Family Group Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Industrial Relations Section; Jan 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Working Together at NCR, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Cash Awards for Good Ideas: NCR Suggestion System, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Working Together at NCR, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Getting Along as a Member of the NCR Family, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Facts You Should Know the First Day at NCR, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Merit and Ability Evaluation, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Evening Classes: 1955-1956 53rd Year, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Information for Our Factory and Office Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: An Educational Opportunity for sons of NCR (National Cash Register Company) Employees: The Annual Deeds Scholarship Award, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: What's Your Idea? Let's Have It!, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Agreement between The NCR (National Cash Register Company) and N.C.R. Employees Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Information and Rules for Our Factory and Office Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: Employee Handbook for NCR Corporate Headquarters Administrative Support Personnel, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: Retirement Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 27: A Plan of Group Insurance, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: The NCR Relief Association Constitution, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: Take Advantage of All NCR Credit Union Services!, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 30: Open A Savings Account In the NCR Credit Union!, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Your Children Can Save Money In A Piggy Bank, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 32: Courses of Instruction 1951-52: NCR Evening Classes 49th Year, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 33: Highlights of the Revised NCR Employee Benefit Program, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 34: Regulation-W: What does this mean to you?, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 35: Owl Classes Twenty-Seventh Year: Announcement of Courses 1929-1930, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 36: 4th Annual Meeting the Twenty-Five Year Glub, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 37: Our Tenth Year of Service, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 38: The Human Side of an Industry, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 39: Highlights of the REVISED NCR Employee Benefit Program, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 40: Accident Prevention and Fire Control, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 41: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 42: NCR Recreational Activities, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 43: Information and Rules For Our Factory and Office Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Box: 88, Folder: 10 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The New NCR Suggestion Contest, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Yellow poster. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statement of Condition as of December 31, 1947, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR Relief Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Write-Up Procedure and the Handling of Forms in the Employment Office, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: NCR Suggestion System, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Suggestion System Report, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Training of Salesmen overview, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By Ewing Stumm. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Salary Policy When Employees are Disabled Because of Accident or Sickness, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Tailored Test to Match Men and Jobs, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Individual Accident Record, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Allen-Wales Training, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By National Cash Register. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Cash Register Training Program, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Employment Requisition, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Packet. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Vacation Notice, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Application for Employment packet, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Accounting Machine Training, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Daily Report, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Yellow chart of transactions. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Discount and Note Control, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By The NCR Employees Credit Union, Inc. Yellow chart with transaction sections. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Discount and Note Control, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By The NCR Employees Credit Union, Inc. Yellow chart with transaction room. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Paycheck/Check, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By The NCR Employees Credit Union, Inc. Packet. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Application for Loan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By The NCR Employees Credit Union, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Information Sheet, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: The Eating of Foods, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Food pyramid. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: 5 Requisites for Life and Health, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: 5 Food Types Necessary for Life, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Management Speaks to its Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By S.C. Allyn, President, NCR (National Cash Register Company). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Labor Turnover Analysis, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: Questionnaire on Age Limit In Industries, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: 1929 Annual Vacation, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By J. H. Barringer. Poster. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Report of the NCR Relief Association for the year ending December 31, 1929, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: $2000 for suggestions First Period, 1927, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Chart. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Information for loans, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By J. H. Barringer. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Application for Membership in the NCR Relief Association, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Application for Membership in the NCR Relief Association, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Outline of vacation plan for 1935, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: Uses and Limitations of Group Incentives, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By R. F. Whisler. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: 1926 Annual Vacation, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: Excerpt from letter re: weekly schedule, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Outline of Plan for the Education of Apprentices, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: Guide for Rating Factory Employees, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: Application for Loan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By NCR Employees Credit Union, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Outline of Plan In Developing and Training tool Making Apprentices, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Dayton Honors NCR on 75th Anniversary, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: NCR Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Employee Indoctrination, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 47: An outstanding record in manufacturing defense equipment of the highest quality, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    By The NCR (National Cash Register Company) and Defense. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Apprentice Training for the NCR (National Cash Register Company), Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Box: 88, Folder: 11 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Sugar Camp 1946, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: NCR Factory News - November 1959, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: NCR Factory News - December 1959, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: NCR Factory News - October 1959, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Welfare Work, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Organizational chart of company, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Welcome to NCR, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Make Your Leisure Time Profitable Through Continued Education for Self-Improvement, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Evening Classes Courses of Instruction. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Talk of the Month: Responsibility of Industry in Community Welfare, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: The Employee and Family Group Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
    By NCR (National Cash Register Company). Bound Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Personnel Policies Manual, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Box: 88, Folder: 12 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: On Guard: The Unsung Story of an Industry in War, Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
    By National Bureau of Industrial Protection. Item is in English.